

Minneapolis, Minnesota <u>www.jackhamby.com</u> 630-240-6317 | <u>jrhamby88@yahoo.com</u>

Profile

Passionate developer who is a constant learner and is not afraid to tackle new challenges. I have been working in a fast paced Agile team for the last 2 years, building full-stack applications with a strong focus on user experience. I have excellent communication skills and am a team player.

Summary of Skills

Languages	Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, C#, C/C++
Databases	MongoDB, PostgreSQL, MySQL
Web Development	Django, Flask, NodeJS, Angular, React, EmberJS
Systems	Git, Unix/Linux, Docker, Kubernetes, OSX, Windows

Experience

Software Engineer

June 2017 - Present

Sansoro Health, Minneapolis, MN

- Designed and built an application for mapping payload data. Provided a GUI and various apis for transforming data from one schema to another. Technologies included Javascript, NodeJS, ExpressJS and Handlebars.
- Redesigned and implemented a monolithic .NET application into cloud-based Kubernetes
 environment by modularizing services into Docker containers, updating to .NET Core, and adding
 logging and settings services using Python.
- Built an **API** design tool for defining product specifications using **JavaScript**, **Python**, **mongoDB**, and **Flask**. This application is used across the company in various departments.
- Added logging and history features to customer portal application. This was a site used by customers to download products and product info. Technologies involved Python, Django and SQLite.
- Built user settings and configuration pages for company's flagship product. This feature is used by customers to manage their production settings.
- Built and designed an application for integrating multiple customer support platforms by aggregating their data and displaying it in a simplified dashboard. The application was used by customer support teams as well as management staff.

Software Engineer - Intern

May 2015 - August 2015

Northfield School District, Northfield, MN

- Built various web pages for volunteer training in the school district.
- Built a volunteer training course from scratch, which included user signup and online training modules.
- Wrote and filmed volunteer training videos with various members of the Northfield community.

Education

St. Olaf College

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

2013 - 2017